const spanish_vocab = [
  { front: "que", back: "that" },
  { front: "de", back: "of, from" },
  { front: "no", back: "no" },
  { front: "a", back: "to" },
  { front: "la", back: "the (feminine singular)" },
  { front: "el", back: "the (masculine singular)" },
  { front: "ser", back: "to be (essential characteristics)" },
  { front: "y", back: "and" },
  { front: "en", back: "in, on" },
  { front: "lo", back: "it, him (direct object)" },
  { front: "un", back: "a (masculine singular)" },
  { front: "por", back: "for, through" },
  { front: "qué", back: "what" },
  { front: "me", back: "me (direct object)" },
  { front: "una", back: "a (female singular)" },
  { front: "te", back: "you (direct object)" },
  { front: "los", back: "the (masucline plural)" },
  { front: "se", back: "himself, herself, itself" },
  { front: "con", back: "with" },
  { front: "para", back: "for, to" },
  { front: "mi", back: "my" },
  { front: "estar", back: "to be (state/location)" },
  { front: "si", back: "if" },
  { front: "bien", back: "good" },
  { front: "pero", back: "but" },
  { front: "yo", back: "I" },
  { front: "eso", back: "that" },
  { front: "las", back: "the (plural feminine" },
  { front: "sí", back: "yes" },
  { front: "su", back: "his, her, its" },
  { front: "tu", back: "your" },
  { front: "aquí", back: "here" },
  { front: "del", back: "of the (masculine singular)" },
  { front: "al", back: "to the (masculine singular)" },
  { front: "como", back: "how" },
  { front: "le", back: "him, her (indirect object)" },
  { front: "más", back: "more" },
  { front: "esto", back: "this (singular masculine" },
  { front: "ya", back: "already" },
  { front: "todo", back: "everything" },
  { front: "esta", back: "this (singular feminine)" },
  { front: "ir", back: "to go" },
  { front: "muy", back: "very" },
  { front: "hay", back: "there is" },
  { front: "ahora", back: "now" },
  { front: "algo", back: "something" },
  { front: "tener", back: "to have" },
  { front: "nos", back: "us" },
  { front: "tú", back: "you" },
  { front: "nada", back: "nothing" },
];

export default spanish_vocab;